No, because I don't want to get a surprise later.
Okay, I will come. I will sit in a place.
I will sit here only. I have to keep a pre-field for that.
And somewhere... actually this is a perfect table.
I have to keep a pre-field.
And somewhere, I need an indication
that how important is this column
to my loan application.
Okay, now how can you do that?
Maybe you can give it stars.
Okay, or you can give it a meter.
Red, orange, green, something like that.
It has become very red.
Okay, or you can give it a score.
10 on 10, 8 on 10, something like that.
But somewhere, tell me how important this column is.
Okay, now what will happen?
Suppose I see 6 columns.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Then I see 4 more columns here.
1, 2, 3, 4. And all are pre-fielded.
Okay, so you don't have to increase the friction.
At the start, I came here.
I have seen 10 columns.
10 on 10 is the consequence.
But everyone has their own like.
That this is less consequential.
This is less consequential.
Okay.
And these 10 are pre-fielded.
And I can see tooltips below.
And it is written in the tooltips.
That if you apply all your existing AMIs to this column,
you will get 10 lakh rupees.
Okay.
I will have no problem filling all these 10 things up.
And on the contrary, I am not doing anything.
I will go somewhere and get my fire ratio out.
And I will get it.
Yes, brother.
Why don't you tell me this?
I feel, at the start,
why I don't want to fill all these fields?
Because I don't know if it will be of any use.
Mine.
But if I see this,
I will get it.
Then I have no problem with 10 fields.
And on the contrary,
we should never write the mandatory fields.
Because later on,
we don't have this with us.
Later on,
it changes.
Because you have existing AMIs.
I have told you that.
And below this,
there is a button.
The name of the button is C-Options.
C-Options.
How did that get derived?
Your items, your options, C-Options.
Okay.
C-Options.
Check.
Compare banks.
Compare banks is an option.
The name of the button is compare banks.
What is explore banks?
Explore works.
Explore means just put everything in.
Do you understand?
That means compare.
Explore doesn't work.
And okay, bro.
If an applicant says yes,
then take their details.
Don't think too much.
What you should do is,
we should think that
the customer doesn't have a problem with the details.
They should feel that
the details are useful.
If you don't do this,
this is a small card.
Most important.
This is red, color or whatever.
Font is big.
And this is the second level card.
And this is the third level card.
And they
get more and more important.
They keep going.
What I feel is,
I don't know the foyer.
But this is not that important.
I will understand that
my loan can be fluctuated.
I told you 8.5.
If I add more foyer,
it can be 8.4 or 8.6.
I will understand this.
And if I don't have this,
I will be a foyer.
If we go to the future,
we have to say that
we need your credit pool.
We don't have to worry at all.
We won't keep anything from us.
We won't prove it to you
that we won't keep anything from you.
I was thinking
that
there are so many requirements.
There are so many things.
Every thing changes
in one age.
The property agreement value
changes only in the loan amount.
The interest rate changes
only in the age and the civil score.
The age, the occupation, the purpose
changes in the tenure.
I was thinking
about the sectioning issue.
about it.
But it is a big issue.
We will have to find a section.
There will be only one section.
But we will have to do a different section.
It is not important
but
we should
in an easy form.
There should be an AI native.
AI native.
Imagine
that
suppose
you
do like this.
Here you have written 10 years.
You give
vertical tabs.
Here you have written 10 years.
This is the tenure with two cards.
And the interest rate
with one card.
How much can you do?
There were four sections.
How many sections?
Let me see.
The rate, amount, tenure.
There were three.
What else?
The section 1.
The section 1 affects.
The rate, amount, tenure.
All three were affected.
The rest of the charges were also affected.
Processing fees, salary,
self-employment.
How many were affected?
It doesn't mean that one thing
affects only one person.
No.
Then no.
Then there is no sectioning.
You mean one-on-one
is not allowed?
Then only.
All are one-on-one.
Like you said earlier,
these two things affect
the loan amount.
But these two things
will also affect
the rest of the people.
Let it be.
But if it is mutually exclusive,
that this only affects the loan amount
and the rest does not affect
the rest of the people,
then we would have
such an intelligent person.
Who would be?
I mean...
How many?